http://www.richardmayer.com/privacy-policy/

Search Our Site
Privacy PolicyWe recognize that you may be concerned about our use and disclosure of your personal information. Your privacy is very important to us, and the following will inform you of the information that we, The Law Offices Of Mayer & Newton, may collect from you, and how it is used. By using our website, www.mayerandnewton.com, you are accepting the practices described in this policy.
Information CollectionWe may collect non-personal information, such as a domain name and IP Address. The domain name and IP address reveals nothing personal about you other than the IP address from which you have accessed our site. We may also collect information about the type of Internet browser you are using, operating system, what brought you to our Website, as well as which of our Web pages you have accessed.Additionally, if you communicate with us regarding our Website or our services, we will collect any information that you provide to us in any such communication.We may contact you via email in the future to tell you about specials, new products or services, or changes to this privacy policy.
Information UseWe use the collected information primarily for our own internal purposes, such as providing, maintaining, evaluating, and improving our services and Website, fulfilling requests for information, and providing customer support.
ConsentBy using this Website, you consent to the collection and use of information as specified above. If we make changes to our Privacy Policy, we will post those changes on this page. Please review this page frequently to remain up-to-date with the information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it. You must review the new Privacy Policy carefully to make sure you understand our practices and procedures.If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, you should contact us immediately via telephone at
(865) 328-7993 or via mail Attn: Privacy Officer, 1111 N Northshore Dr., Suite S-570, Knoxville, TN 37919.
865-328-7993
Follow Us
Knoxville Office
865-328-7993
1111 N Northshore Dr.,
2298 Sandstone Dr.
Morristown, TN 37814
Map & Directions
Sevierville Office
865-344-6968
100 E Main St.,
The information on this website is for general information purposes only.
Nothing on this site should be taken as legal advice for any individual
case or situation. This information is not intended to create, and receipt
or viewing does not constitute, an attorney-client relationship.
© 2020 All Rights Reserved.
